Joey : That wasn't a real date.
Joey : What the hell do you do on a real date?
Monica : Shut up and put my table back.
unknown : Okay.
Chandler : All right, kids, I gotta get to work.
Chandler : If I don't input those numbers, doesn't make much of a difference.
Rachel : So, like, you guys all have jobs?
Monica : Yeah, we all have jobs.
Monica : See, that's how we buy stuff.
Joey : Yeah, I'm an actor.
unknown : Wow.
Rachel : What, I've seen you in anything?
unknown : Oh, I doubt it.
Joey : Mostly regional work.
Monica : Oh, hey, unless you happen to catch the Wee Ones production of Pinocchio.
Chandler : Look, Geppetto, I'm a real live boy.
Joey : I will not take this abuse.
Chandler : You're right, I'm sorry.